A Guide to the Grayson Genealogical Collection, 1728 (1927-1950)
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Grayson Genealogical Collection, 1728 (1927-1950)
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
9018
120 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
The collection was loaned to the Library by Mrs. W. D. Haden of "Farmington," Charlottesville, Virginia, on November 1, 1960.
Biographical/Historical Information
Mrs. Jennie Grayson was a genealogist.
Scope and Content Information
This collection contains ca. 120 genealogical items, 1728 (1927-1950), of various Virginia families, compiled by Mrs. Jennie Grayson for her clients. She also dealt with genealogies for the Daughters of the American Revolution and the Daughters of the Confederacy. There is also a copy of The Handbook of American Genealogy.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged alphabetically.
Contents List
- Letters to Mrs. Grayson 1928-1950, n.d.
- Genealogies A-D: Baker, Berryman, Boatwright, Burrass, Bustee, Carpenter, Clark, Craig, Curtis n.d.
- Genealogies E-Z: Decker, Davis, Dowell, Eonery, Eppenon, Eppes, Field, Fox, Hartley, Howard, Joplin, Johnson, King, Mapp, Marshall, McGregor, Randolph, Wallace, Whitehead, Whittlock n.d.
- Ball and related families 1933, n.d.
- Brown and related families. n.d.
- Clarkson and related families n.d.
- Clayton and related families 1936, n.d.
- Coleman and related families 1935, n.d.
- Coles and related families 1927
- Dick, Westcott and related families; see also Godwin 1932-1934, n.d.
- Dyer and related families n.d.
- Godwin and related families; see also Dick and Westcott 1934, n.d.
- Haden and related families n.d.
- Israel and related families 1943, n.d.
- Jacob and related families n.d.
- Jefferson and related families n.d.
- Jennings and related families 1924-1927, n.d.
- Jones and related families 1932-1948, n.d.
- Jewett and related families 1939, n.d.
- Lee and related families 1728 (1935-1945), n.d.
- Lewis and related families n.d.
- Peck and related families n.d.
- Westcott family 1934
- Wodrop and related families 1934
- The Handbook of American Genealogy by Frederick Vikus 1932